IACOB BOGDAN

Remote | lasi

(+40) 720 587 120 bogdan1.iacob@gmail.com linkedin.com/bogdan-iacob/ bOgdan-iacob.github.io/profile/

ABOUT ME

Full stack web developer with a degree in System Engeneering and 5 years of experience and a passion for building software that drives change.

Awords

- Winner, ITMarathon Hackathon Grand Prize. Project selected over 100 other participants.
- Winner, "Student Scientific Communications Session" - Web technologies with "The use of blockchain technology in the context of industry 4.0" 3d place.

Core Skills

JavaScript, jQuery, Java/J2EE with Spring, ReactJS, Angular, PHP with Laravel, SQL, NodeJS, Vue, Docker, MongoDB, AWS Cloud Services, Linux, Swift, GIT, Jenkins CI/CD, Ansible.

EXPERIENCE

P3Software

Full Stack Web Developer | Feb, 2022 - Present

- Worked on the integration of the new cost-efficient booking engine p3essential providing customers with a fully integrated booking solution including reservations and secure payment integration.
- Developing the booking systems, online check-in and check-out systems for new clients and implementing the
 required new functionalities to feature uplift conversion rate and improve direct booking revenue.

Signant Health

Aplication Specialist | Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

- Designed and Deployed client oriented Electronic Clinical Outcome Assessments solutions using TrialStudio, TrialMax and Patient Engagement platforms that deliver accurate data for near real-time analyses providing them with a competitive edge on the medical market.
- Created guides to document the processes and maintain operational continuity.

Directorate of Informatization and Digital Communications - TUIASI

Full Stack Web Developer | Nov 2018 - Sep 2021

- Involved in design, development and deployment of the TUIASI Student Management System that ensures easy administration of over 20000 students from 16 faculty.
- Developed the payment portal taxe.tuiasi.ro for students and professors to be able to pay all their tuition fees, related to the didactic activity, as well as campus fees, in full online.
- Worked on extension of the Online Admission System for "Gheorghe Asachi" Techincal University of lasi
 facilitating the admission of over 3000 students annually with an boost of 30% more applicants over the
 traditional process of admission.
- Built and maintain numerous websites such as international.tuiasi.ro, opendays.ro, study-programmes.tuiasi.ro with with thousands of visitors.
- Extended Erasmus application used by students which participate at Erasmus project in collaboration with TUIASI.
- Designed and implemented an Kiosk type system around the university academic campus providing information, directions and newsletter.

EDUCATION

Master's degree in CyberSpace Security | present

Faculty of Automatic Control and Computer Engineering

Bachelor of Computer Science - SystemEngineering

Faculty of Automatic Control and Computer Engineering

REFERENCES

Available on request